itools.com 2004-12-10

# iTools Privacy Statement

> iTools respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement.
> 
> ### Information Collection and Use
>
>> **Personally Identifiable Information**  
>  iTools does not collect personally identifiable information from our users on our Web site.
>
>> **Cookies**  
>  iTools does not employ cookies on our site.
>
>> **Log Files**  
>  Like all Web site servers we use log files which record the internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring pages, platform type and date/time stamp of page requests. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use the log files to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
> 
> ### Third Party Advertising
>
>> The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by a third-party Web advertising partner. Information about users’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site.
>
>> These third-party advertising partners may employ cookies. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
> 
> ### Links
>
>> This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.
> 
> ### Contact Information
>
>> If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact our Privacy Group by sending an email to [webprivacy@itools.com](mailto:webprivacy@itools.com)

This page is http://www.itools.com/info/privacy/
